Marguerite Higgins Papers
Marguerite Higgins Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Publicity
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1953; 1961 (Box 44)
      See also Box 47 for poster
    - Newsday, 1963-1964 (Box 44)
    - Die Welt, undated (Box 44)
  - Promotional Advertising
    - Camel cigarette ad, undated (Box 44)
  - Reviews
    - Our Vietnam Nightmare, 1965; clippings (Box 44)
    - Overtime in Heaven, 1964; clippings (Box 44)
    - War in Korea, 1951; clippings (Box 44)
  - Miscellaneous
    - [Assorted ephemera], 1952-1954 (Box 44)
      Invitation lists for a "Welcome to Washington Party" for Sen. Edmondson and a reception for Mr. And Mrs. Carl T. Rowan; paper target from Higgins first lesson in rifle marksmanship (signed by Lt. Gen. Hall); one sheet of Higgins' stationery; Authors Guild membership certificate and by-laws; publication: "Raising a family is a pleasure."
  - Scrapbooks
    - [No. 1], "Europe Marguerite Higgins 1944-1945-1946", news clips (Box 51)
    - [No. 2], "Marg. Higgins 25 Jan. '46 Dec. '46 - July '47", news clips (Box 51)
    - [No. 3], "Russell Hill Jan. '46-July '46/Marg. Higgins July '47-31 Jan. '48", news clips (Box 51)
    - [No. 4], "Cuttings - Herald TribuneFeb. 1 '48", news clips (Box 52)
    - [No. 5], "Clippings - New York Times 4 June 1948-Aug. 24" (Box 52)
    - [No. 6], Clippings - New York Times Aug 25", 1948 (Box 53)
    - [No. 7], [News clips], 10/21/48-1/1/51; Higgins and others (Box 54)
    - [No. 8], [News clips], May 1951 - Nov. 1951; clips about Higgins (Box 54)
    - [No. 9], [Russia clips], 1955 (Box 54)
    - [No. 10], "Marguerite Higgins interviews with world leaders 2/19/53 to 6/21/53" (Box 54)
    - [No. 11], "Marguerite Higgins Far Eastern tour 6/22/53 to 9/19/53" (Box 54)
    - [No. 12], [News clips], 11/2/63 - 4/3/64 (Box 55)
    - [No. 13], "Vietnam 11/?/63 - 2/26/65", Higgins' columns and articles (Box 55)
    - [No. 14], "Newsday Articles 2/19/64-6/1/64", Higgins' column and articles (Box 56)
    - [No. 15], "Newsday Articles 5/29/64-9/9/64", Higgins' column and articles (Box 56)
    - [No. 16], "Articles as they appear in the Evening Star", 9/2/64-3/10/65; Higgins' columns (Box 57)
    - [No. 17], "The Evening Star and Others", 3/22/65-8/30/65; Higgins' columns (Box 57)
    - [No. 18], "The Evening Star and other papers from Sept. 1, 1965", 9/1/65-12/16/65; Higgins' columns (Box 58)
    - [No. 19], [News clips], 9/11/64-12/31/65; Higgins' columns (Box 58)